<?xml version='1.0' ?>

<news>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/04/12
    </date>
    <text>
      Again the homepage has been redesigned (mainly internal). Most noteably
      difference: the downloadscript works much better now, you don't have
      to rename the file in your filerequester anymore.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/03/25
    </date>
    <text>
      Introduced the new SimpleMail <a href="index.html?galery">User Gallery</a>.
      Alpha 0.5 has been released. New features are:
      <list>
        <item>Configurable mail download selection added.</item>
        <item>Supports 8 bit mime mails (if a SMTP Server don't support them they are encoded on the fly).</item>
        <item>Improved the readwindow. Now used extensivly the SimpleHTML engine.</item>
        <item>Button images are cached now.</item>
        <item>Support of the new SimpleMail User Gallery.</item>
      </list>
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/02/25
    </date>

    <text>
      A new alpha 0.4 has been released. Most important new feature is the possibility to
      configure more then one POP3 server.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/02/09
    </date>

    <text>
      I (Hynek) am leaving today and will come back in April so send all mail you
      send to me also to Sebastian as he will stay here.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/02/06
    </date>

    <text>
      New frequently asked questions added to the <a href="index.html?part=faq">FAQ</a>.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/02/05
    </date>

    <text>
      Alpha-Version 0.3 released! This time we have added quiet a bunch of new
      features:
      <list>
        <item>Forward button.</item>
        <item>The main window has two different views which are switchable
          within the mainwindow.</item>
        <item>Improved the composewindow (some buttons added, also a undo/redo).</item>
        <item>The "To" button in the addressbook works now.</item>
        <item>Group mails (mails with multiple recipients), mails with attachments,
          important mails can now easily identified.</item>
        <item>Added a small context menu for the mailtreelist, mails can now be
          marked and hold.</item>
        <item>Added the possibility to use your IP-addresss as you domain in
          the HELO/EHLO dialog. (no X-Authentification-Warning headers anymore).</item>
        <item>Added smtp-auth according to rfc2554.</item>
        <item>It is now possible to specify which port you would like to use on
          the servers instead of 25 (SMTP) and 110 (POP3).</item>
        <item>Other smaller improvements and bug fixes.</item>
      </list>
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/01/26
    </date>

    <text>
      New frequently asked question added to the <a href="index.html?faq">FAQ</a>.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/01/26
    </date>

    <text>
      Added some banners for your homepages made by Richard Wagenführer.
      You can find them in the <a href="index.html?downloads">downloads-section</a>.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/01/23
    </date>

    <text>
      The homepage moves to http://simplemail.sourceforge.net/. A completly new
      design is introduced.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2001/01/14
    </date>

    <text>
      The second alpha version 0.2 is released.
    </text>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <date>
      2000/12/24
    </date>

    <text>
      The first alpha version 0.1 is released.
    </text>
  </entry>

</news>
