<?xml version='1.0' encoding="iso-8859-1"?>

<news>

  <entry date="2009/12/24">
   <text lang="en">
    A new version of SimpleMail has been released! Version 0.35
    comes with following changes
    <list>
    <item>New ARexx commands: MAILDELETE, MAILMOVE, MAILSETSTATUS, and VERSION 
    </item>
    <item>Added new column in the mail list: Excerpt</item>
    <item>Added a new search option: Body</item>
    <item>New command line arguments: PROFILEDIR and IMAGEDIR</item>
    <item>Fixed a bunch of bugs and memory leaks</item>
    </list>
     The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry Christmas and a happy new year 2009! 
   </text>
   
   <text lang="de">

		Eine neue Version von SimpleMail wurde soeben veröffentlicht. Die Änderungen seit 
		Version 0.33 sind:

    <list>
    <item>Neue ARexx-Kommandos: MAILDELETE, MAILMOVE, MAILSETSTATUS und VERSION</item>
    <item>Eine neue Spalte in der Nachrichtenliste gibt einen Auszug der Nachrichten wieder.</item>
    <item>Die Suche kann nun auch auf den Inhalt von Nachrichten angewandt werden.</item>
    <item>Neue Kommandozeilen-Argumente: PROFILEDIR und IMAGEDIR.</item>
    <item>Einige Fehler wurden entfernt, insbesondere wurden viele Speicherlecks beseitigt.</item>
    </list>
    
    Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen fröhliche Weihnachten und einen guten Rutsch ins neue Jahr!
   
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2008/12/24">
   <text lang="en">
    Just in time a new version of SimpleMail has been released! The new
    version 0.33 comes with the following changes
    <list>
    <item>Quick filter now highlights the first occurrence of the string
     within all cells in the mail list
    </item>
    <item>Maillist now supports alternating background colors for rows.
     This feature can be controlled by three new hidden options:
       Hidden.DontDrawAlternatingRows,
       Hidden.RowBackground, and
       Hidden.AltRowBackground.
    </item>
    <item>Fixed some critical bugs in the SimpleHTML engine</item>
    <item> POP3 feature "Avoid duplicates" should now work better when using
     multiple accounts on the same server.
    </item>
    <item>Improved IMAP support</item>
    <item>Incoming mails are no longer added by one into the mail tree list</item>
    <item>Added functions such as "Save All Attachments", "Select All Messages",
     and "Clear Selection" to improve general usability a little bit
     </item>
    </list>
     The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry Christmas and a happy new year 2009! 
   </text>
   
   <text lang="de">

    Pünktlich zur Weihnachtszeit wurde eine neue Version von SimpleMail veröffentlicht!
    Die Änderungen in Version 0.33 lauten:

    <list>
    <item>Bei aktivierter Schnellfilteroption werden die passenden Textstellen hervorgehoben
    </item>
    <item>Die Zeilen der Nachrichtenliste werden nun mit abwechselnden Farben unterlegt.
     Die Fähigkeit kann mit den folgenden versteckten Optionen in der Konfigurationsdatei beeinflusst werden
       Hidden.DontDrawAlternatingRows,
       Hidden.RowBackground, and
       Hidden.AltRowBackground.
    </item>
    <item>Einige kritische Fehler in der SimpleHTML behoben.</item>
    <item>Die Option "Duplikate vermeiden" sollte nun besser mit mehreren, sich auf den gleichen Server beziehenden 
          Kontos funktionieren.
    </item>
    <item>IMAP-Unterstützung verbessert</item>
    <item>Eingehende Nachrichten werden nun zusammengefasst in die Nachrichtenliste eingefügt.</item>
    <item>Neue einfache Funktionen wie "Alle Dateianhänge speichern", "Alle Nachrichten auswählen" und
    "Auswahl aufheben" hinzugefügt.
     </item>
    </list>
    
    Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen fröhliche Weihnachten und einen guten Rutsch ins neue Jahr!
   
   </text>
   
   
  </entry>
  <entry date="2007/12/24">
   <text lang="en">

    And here is the Christmas and birthday release of SimpleMail. In brief, the release 0.32 of SimpleMail
    is characterized by the following changes:

	  <list>
     <item>Partly supports AISS. Can be disabled by using the Hidden.DontUseAISS hidden configuration option.</item>
     <item>Completed functionality of custom mail list, e.g., columns can be reordered, their state saved, and so on.</item>
     <item>Added quick filter.</item>
     <item>Bug fixes.</item>
    </list>

    The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry christmas and a happy new year! 

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    Die Weihnachts- und Geburtstagsversion von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen in Version 0.32 betreffen:

	  <list>
     <item>AISS wird in Teilen unterstützt. Die Benutzung von AISS kann mit Hilfe der Konfigurationoption Hidden.DontUseAISS verhindert werden.</item>
     <item>Die Funktionalität der eigenen Nachrichtenlistenklasse wurde komplettiert. Beispielsweise können Spalten umgeordnet und der Zustand gespeichert werden.</item>
     <item>Schnellfilteroption im Hauptfenster hinzugefügt.</item>
     <item>Einige Bugfixes.</item>
    </list>

    Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen fröhliche Weihnachten und einen guten Rutsch ins Jahr 2008!

   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2007/02/05">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.31 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

    <list>
     <item> Replaced the usage of the NList class by the mail list with the usage of a custom list. It should act like NList, but
     switching through folders should be a lot of faster now. Also it allows further improvments to the mail list.
     The new SIMPLEMAIL_OLDMAILLIST environment variable can be used to stick to the NList class usage. (bgol, sba)
     </item>
     <item>New config option "Folder to display at startup" (bgol)</item>
     <item>Filter improved (bgol)</item>
     <item>Double buffering of simplehtml engine can be disabled via SIMPLEHTML_NODOUBLEBUFFER environment variable.</item>
     <item> Minor fixes in the simplehtml engine.</item>
    </list>
   </text>
   <text lang="de">
     Version 0.31 von SimpleMail veröffentlicht!
     
     Die Änderungen seit der letzten Version sind:

    <list>
     <item> Die Nachrichtenliste benutzt nun eine eigenene Listklasse anstelle von NList. Die neue Klasse sollte sich ähnlich wie
            NList verhalten, aber einen Geschwindkeitsschub mit sich bringen. Desweiteren werden hierdurch weitere Verbesserung ermöglicht.
            Mittels der neuen SIMPLEMAIL_OLDMAILLIST Umgebungsvariable kann das alte Verhalten herbeigeführt werden.
     </item>
     <item>Möglichkeit, einen beliebigen Ordner nach Programmstart anzuzeigen, hinzugefügt (bgol).</item>
     <item>Verbesserte Filter (bgol)</item>
     <item>Double-Buffering der SimpleHTML-Engine kann nun mittels SIMPLEHTML_NODOUBLEBUFFER Umgebungsvariable deaktiviert werden.</item>
     <item>Kleinere Bugfixes in der SimpleHTML-Engine.</item>
    </list>
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2006/12/24">
   <text lang="en">

    Here again we present the christmas release of SimpleMail. However, due to many
    time contraints on the part of the authors only minor issues could be addressed
    this time.

	  The changes for version 0.30 were:

	  <list>
	   <item>Minor fixes in the html display (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Previewed mails are now marked as read after a certain amount of time.</item>
	   <item>Minor fixes in the index creation code.</item>
    </list>

    The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry christmas and a happy new year! 

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    Die Weihnachtsversion von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen in Version 0.30 betreffen:

	  <list>
	   <item>Kleine Bugs in der HTML Anzeige entfernt.</item>
	   <item>Nachrichten im Vorschaufenster werden als gelesen markiert.</item>
	   <item>Bug beim Indexerstellen entfernt.</item>
    </list>

    Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen ein frohes und besinnliches Weihnachtsfest und einen guten Rutsch ins neue Jahr!

   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2006/02/05">
   <text lang="en">

	  Version 0.29 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

	  <list>
 		<item>E-mail addresses within the mails can be added to the addressbook now (only within mail preview). </item>
 		<item>Added support of AmigaOS patterns to the filter rules. (bgol)</item>
 		<item>Added possibility to skip the server which is currently being processed.</item>
		<item>Finally added BCC support and email importance setting (bgol)</item>
		<item>Bug fixes (printing and other stuff)</item>
	  </list>

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.29 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:

	  <list>
 		<item>E-Mail Adressen innerhalb von Nachrichten können nun ins Adressbuch hinzugefügt werden (nur im Vorschaufenster). </item>
 		<item>Filter unterstützen nun AmigaOS Muster. (bgol)</item>
 		<item>Server können beim Runter- bzw. Hochladen übersprungen werden.</item>
		<item>BCC und Wichtigkeit hinzufügt. (bgol)</item>
		<item>Fehlerbereinigungen (u.a. das Umlautproblem beim Drucken).</item>
      </list>

   </text>
  </entry>


  <entry date="2005/12/24">
   <text lang="en">

    As it is already tradition, a new version of SimpleMail has been released
    at XMas and it is also SimpleMail's 5th anniversary this time!

	  The changes for version 0.28 were:

	  <list>
	   <item>Printing problems fixed (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Time for the next autocheck is displayed within the window title (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Added some more read window options (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Mails can be optionally forwarded as attachments.</item>
	   <item>Added "Project/Open message..." menu entry allowing the user to
           view mails which are stored externally. Similar function is
           provided by the command line and by the OPENMESSAGE ARexx
          command.</item>
     <item>bug fixes</item>
    </list>

    The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry christmas and a happy new year! 

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    Wie es schon Tradition ist, wurde auch dieses Jahr zu Weihnachten
    eine neue SimpleMail Version veröffentlicht. Zeitgleich ist es
    auch der fünfte Geburtstag des Programms!

	  Die Änderungen seit der letzten Version sind:

	  <list>
	   <item>Probleme beim Drucken behoben (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Die Zeit bis zum nächsten (automatischen) Nachrichtendownload wird im Fenstertitel angezeigt (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Einige Optionen für das Verhalten des Lesefensters hinzugefügt (bgol).</item>
	   <item>Nachrichten können optional als Anhänge weitergeleitet werden.</item>
	   <item>Extern abgelegte Nachrichten können mittels neuem Menüpunkt "Projekt/Nachricht öffnen..." dargestellt werden.
           Die selbe Funktion gibt es bei der Kommandozeile und durch das ARexx-Kommando "OPENMESSAGE".</item>
     <item>Fehlerbereinigungen</item>
    </list>

    Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen ein frohes und besinnliches Weihnachtsfest und einen guten Rutsch ins neue Jahr!

   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2005/04/17">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.27 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
   	<list>
     <item>fixed some problems in the morphos build (henes)</item>
     <item>a number of bugs fixes</item>
    </list>
   </text>

   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.27 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
   	<list>
     <item>Einige Probleme innhalb der MorphOS Version wurden behoben (henes)</item>
     <item>Weitere Fehlerbereinigungen</item>
    </list>
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2005/03/13">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.26 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
   	<list>
     <item>optional TheBar.mcc is now used for all toolbars (bgol)</item>
     <item>compacted mailinfo shows now additional the from field (bgol)</item>
     <item>simplehtml.library ported to OS4</item>
     <item>Fixed broken SMTP STARTTLS support</item>
     <item>Minor other improvements and fixes</item>
    </list>
   </text>

   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.26 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
   	<list>
     <item>Optionale TheBar.mcc wird nun für alle Toolbars verwendet (bgol)</item>
     <item>Kompakte Form der Nachrichtenkenndaten zeigt nun zusätzlich das Absenderfeld</item>
     <item>simplehtml.library nach OS4 portiert</item>
     <item>Probleme mit SMTP STARTTLS behoben</item>
     <item>Minor other improvements and fixes</item>
    </list>
   </text>
  </entry>


  <entry date="2005/02/05">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.25 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
   	<list>
   	 <item> RFC 3490 support for domains of email addresses.</item>
   	 <item> The mail preview no longer embeds the mail header but displays it
   	 		separatly. This can be switched to a compact form to save space.</item>
	 <item> Multiple imap accounts (with different logins) per imap server are now possible.</item>
     <item> If available "TheBar.mcc" is now used (for the main toolbar only)</item>
     <item> Bug fixes and other improvements</item>
   	</list>
   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.25 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
   	<list>
   	 <item> RFC 3490 wird nun für Domänen von eMail Adressen unterstützt.</item>
   	 <item> Informationen der Nachrichten werden nun separat in der Vorschauanzeige dargestellt.
   	        Dies kann auf eine kompakte Form umgeschalten werden, um Platz zu sparen.</item>
	 <item> Mehrere IMAP Konten mit unterschiedlichen Logins pro IMAP server sind nun möglich.</item>
     <item> Falls verfügbar, wird die "TheBar.mcc" für die Toolbar des Hauptfensters benutzt.</item>
     <item> Fehlerbereinigungen und andere kleinere Verbesserungen.</item>
   	</list>
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2004/12/24">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.24 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
    <list>
    <item>Mail preview in main window</item>
    <item>Outlook Express mail folder import (.dbx files)</item>
    <item>New addressbook with separated groups and contacts</item>
    <item>More application icon configuration possibilities (bgol)</item>
    <item>ARexx Port improvements: GETMAILSTAT, FOLDERINFO (bgol)</item>
    <item>Bug fixes and minor other improvements (bgol, henes and me)</item>
    <item>First official OS4 release</item>
    </list>

    The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry christmas and a happy new year! We hope you have fun with
    the new release!

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.24 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:

    <list>
    <item>Nachrichtenvorschau im Hauptfenster</item>
    <item>Importieren von Outlook Express Nachrichtdateien (.dbx Dateien)</item>
    <item>Neues Adressbuch mit separierter Gruppen- und Kontakteverwaltung</item>
    <item>Mehr Möglichkeiten, das Applikationsicon zu konfigurieren (bgol)</item>
    <item>ARexx-Port Verbesserungen: GETMAILSTAT, FOLDERINFO (bgol)</item>
    <item>Bug Fixes und andere kleine Verbesserungen (bgol, henes, sba)</item>
    <item>Erste offizielle OS4 Version</item>
    </list>
   </text>

   Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen ein frohes und besinnliches Weihnachtsfest und einen guten Rutsch ins neue Jahr! Viel Spaß mit der neuen Version.

  </entry>

  <entry date="2004/02/05">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.23 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

    <list>
    <item>AppIcon support (bgol)</item>
    <item>mbox files can be imported to selected folders directly (bgol)</item>
    <item>APOP support</item>
    <item>Ported to MorphOS (henes)</item>
    <item>Bug fixes</item>
    </list>
   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.23 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:

    <list>
    <item>AppIcon Unterstützung (bgol)</item>
    <item>mbox Dateien können in direkt in einen selektierten Ordner importiert werden (bgol)</item>
    <item>APOP Unterstützung</item>
    <item>Nach MorphOS portiert(henes)</item>
    <item>Bug Fixes</item>
    </list>
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2004/01/01">
   <text lang="en">

	  Version 0.22 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

    <list>
      <item>Signatures can now be chooses on a per account and per folder base (bgol)</item>
      <item>No longer needs to load the indexfile if you move mails to a folder</item>
      <item>From field always missed the Realname. Fixed.</item>
      <item>Happy new Year 2004!</item>
    </list>

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.22 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
    <list>
     <item>Signaturen können nun für jeden Ordner und Konto separat eingestellt werden. (bgol)</item>
     <item>Indexdateien des Zielordner werden bei der Verschiebeoperation nicht länger geladen.</item>
     <item>From Feld hatte keinen Realnamen mehr. Behoben.</item>
     <item>Ein gesundes neues Jahr 2004!</item>
    </list>

   </text>
  </entry>


  <entry date="2003/12/24">
   <text lang="en">

	  Version 0.21 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

    <list>
     <item>Can import mbox files</item>
     <item>Fixed memory leaks (bgol) </item>
     <item>Layout of important list elememts are now stored via "Settings/Save Settings" too (bgol)</item>
     <item>Basic Remote Filter: Mails which matches a filter are ignored</item>
     <item>SimpleHTML support code is now inside a shared library</item>
     <item>Ported to OS4</item>
     <item>Describes now how spam itentfication can be used within the guide</item>
     <item>Bug fixes and minor other improvements (see trackers at sf)</item>
    </list>


    The SimpleMail Team wishes you all a merry christmas and a happy new year!

   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.21 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
    <list>
     <item>Importieren vom mbox Dateien ist nun möglich</item>
     <item>Verschiedene Speicherlecks behoben (bgol) </item>
     <item>Das Layout wichtiger Listelmente kann nun mittels "Einstellungen/Einstellungen speichern" gesichert werden (bgol)</item>
     <item>Einfacher Remote Filter: Bestimmte Nachrichten können auf dem Server gelassen werden</item>
     <item>SimpleHTML Unterstützung ist nun in einer Shared Library</item>
     <item>Nach OS4 portiert</item>
     <item>Anleitung beschreibt wie die Spam Identifikation funktioniert</item>
     <item>Bug Fixes und andere kleinere Verbesserungen (siehe Tracker auf sf)</item>
    </list>


    Das SimpleMail Team wünscht allen ein frohes und besinnliches Weihnachtsfest und einen guten Rutsch ins neue Jahr!

   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2003/09/07">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.20 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

    <list>
		<item>Can now download mails from an imap server partly</item>
		<item>Added an statistcal spam filter</item>
		<item>Lots of other minor improvements and bug fixes (see trackers at sourceforge page)</item>
    </list>
   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.20 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
    <list>
		<item>Nachrichten von einem Imap Server können nun teilweise heruntergeladen werden</item>
		<item>Statistischer Spam Filter hinzugefügt</item>
		<item>Viele andere kleine Verbesserungen und Bug fixes (siehe Tracker auf SourceForge)</item>
    </list>
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2003/02/05">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.19 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:

    <list>
    <item>PGP works again as it did (encrypt/decrypt)</item>
    <item>moving through mails updates their state again (Bernd Gollesch)</item>
    <item>proper secodary sort support (Bernd Gollesch)</item>
    <item>Can read signed S/MIME mails properly (displaing them at least, needs AmiSSL)</item>
    <item>importing the addressbook of YAM works for newer versions too</item>
    <item>Other bug fixes</item>
    </list>
   </text>
   <text lang="de">
    SimpleMail Version 0.19 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
    <list>
    <item>PGP funktioniert wieder wie vor 0.18 (ver- und entschlüsseln)</item>
    <item>Beim Bewegen durch die Mails im Lesefeneter wird der Status wieder richtig aktualisiert (Bernd Gollesch)</item>
    <item>Sekundäre Sortiermodus ist jetzt richtig implementiert (Bernd Gollesch)</item>
    <item>Signierte S/MIME Nachrichten werden vernünftig angezeigt (AmiSSL wird benötigt)</item>
    <item>Das Adressbuch von neueren Version zu importieren funktioniert nun</item>
    <item>Andere Fehlerbeseitigungen</item>
    </list>
   </text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2002/12/24">
	<text lang="en">
    Accurately two years, after SimpleMail saw the light of the world we can present
    again a XMas release of SimpleMail with some hopfully great new featues. Again we
    have to thank you for your continuos support and encouragement very much.
    
    The SimpleMail Team wishes a merry christmas and a happy new year! Enjoy
    the new version

    The changes are:
    <list>
    <item>Folder/Export... menu entry added to export a complete mail folder</item>
    <item>Added recpient filter rule type (which matches To and CC)</item>
		<item>Internal multithreading changes (no longer relies on SAS C CRES startup code></item>
    <item>now uses the shared version of the expat XML engine (included)</item>
		<item>(temporary) rejected NListtree support for the mail view because it slowed down everything</item>
    <item>very simple IMAP support (fetches complete mail, no move support, no status update)</item>
    <item>bug fixes as usual</item>
    </list>

    Please also install the latest NList and NListtree MUI classes. Older versions than current may cause
    too much problems. Get them from <A HREF="http://home.t-online.de/home/sebauer">http://home.t-online.de/home/sebauer</A>
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
		Heute sind es exakt zwei Jahre seit dem SimpleMail das Licht der Welt erblickt hat. Wieder
		können wir ein XMas Release von SimpleMail bescheren die einige hoffentlich interesante neue
		Features zu bieten hat. Wir möchten uns an der Stelle ebenfalls für den vielen Zuspruch den
		wir erfahren haben bedanken und wünschen allen ein frohes Weihnachtsfest und einen guten Rutsch
		ins neue Jahr.

		Die Änderungen:
    <list>
    <item>Folder/Exportieren... Menü Eintag zum Exportieren eines Mailverzeichnisses</item>
    <item>Empfänger Filter Regeltyp hinzugefügt (steht für TO oder CC)</item>
		<item>Interne Änderuung des Multithreading</item>
    <item>Die Shared Version der expat.library wird benutzt (im Archiv enthalten)</item>
		<item>NListtree Unterstützung der Nachrichtenliste (vorerst) entfernt (verlangsamte alles)</item>
    <item>Ganz einfache IMAP Unterstützung (nur komplette Nachricht, kein Bewegen, keien Statusänderungen)</item>
    <item>Wie immer einen Haufen Bugfixes</item>
    </list>

		Zu beachten ist, dass immer die neuesten NList bzw. NListtree Klassen installiert sind, andernfalls kann 
		es zu vermehrten Problemen bei der Darstellung führen. Die MUI Klassen gibts auf <A HREF="http://home.t-online.de/home/sebauer">http://home.t-online.de/home/sebauer</A>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2002/09/07">
	<text lang="en">
	  Version 0.17 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
	  <list>
    <item>shows user@popserver in the check single account sub menu</item>
    <item>added possibility to add the recpient of an e-mail later</item>
    <item>closing the compose window will not discard the current edited mail</item>
    <item>search function added</item>
		</list>
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  SimpleMail Version 0.17 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
	  <list>
    <item>Zeigt nun user@popserver im Einzelnes Kontoaufrufen Untermenü</item>
    <item>Empfängeradresse der Nachrichten kann nun auch später festgelegt werden</item>
    <item>Beim Schließen des Nachrichtenschreibfenster wird die Nachricht nun nicht gesichert, anstatt sie zu löschen</item>
    <item>Suchfunktion hinzugefügt</item>
		</list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2002/05/25">
	<text lang="en">
	  Version 0.16 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
	  <list>
    <item>requires version 18.12 of NListtree</item>
    <item>speed up within the mail list</item>
    <item>scrollbars in readwindow for datatypes</item>
    <item>you can drag attachments from the readwindow and drop them on to the workbench now (requires OS3.9)</item>
    <item>New Config option: Possibilty that SimpleMail only auto downloads if Miami is online</item>
    <item>New Config option: Execute an ARexx script if new mails has been arrived</item>
    <item>New Config option: Download at startup</item>
    <item>New Filter actions: Play sound and execute an arexx script</item>
    <item>No longer popups the error window if aborting</item>
    <item>bug fixes</item>
		</list>
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  SimpleMail Version 0.16 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
	  <list>
    <item>benötigt die Version 18.12 des NListtree</item>
    <item>schnellere Maillist</item>
    <item>Scrollbars im Lesefenster für Datatypes</item>
    <item>Drag und Drop vom Lesefenster in die Workbench (benötigt OS3.9)</item>
    <item>Ein paar neue Konfig Optionen auf der Mailemfangeseite</item>
    <item>Zwei neue Filteraktionen</item>
    <item>Besserer Abbruch beim Mailladen/emfangen</item>
    <item>Bug Fixes</item>
		</list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2002/02/05">
	<text lang="en">
	  Version 0.15 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
	  <list>
    <item>Internally most strings are utf8 now. Note: Maybe I missed some utf8 to iso conversion and you will see some text bugs</item>
		<item>User can/should select the charset now which he uses on his system</item>
		<item>Some new translations</item>
		<item>Two new columns in the maillist: "POP3 Server", "Received"</item>
		<item>Slight layout change of the compose window</item>
		<item>Supports "Content-Description:" field</item>
		<item>Bug fixes as usual</item>
		</list>
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  SimpleMail Version 0.15 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
	  <list>
    <item>SimpleMail wurde intern auf Unicode umgestellt</item>
		<item>Man kann bzw. sollte nun die Zeichentabelle wählen, die auf dem System benutzt wird</item>
		<item>Neue Übersetzungen hinzugefügt</item>
		<item>Zwei neue Spalten in der Nachrichtenliste: "POP3 Server" und "Emfangen"</item>
		<item>Kleine Layoutänderungen im Nachrrichtenschreibfenster</item>
		<item>"Content-Description:" Feld wird unterstützt</item>
		<item>Einige Fehler wurden beseitigt</item>
		</list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/12/24">
	<text lang="en">
	  If you have problems with opening the prefs window and have downloaded the
	  archive before 4:00pm CET, please download it again, the optimizer of SAS/C
	  seems to be broken. :(
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Falls Sie Probleme haben, das Prefs-Fenster zu öffnen und das Archiv vor 16:00
	  Uhr MEZ heruntergeladen haben, dann laden Sie es bitte nochmal herunter, da der
	  Optimizer von SAS/C anscheinend fehlerhaft arbeitet. :(
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/12/24">
	<text lang="en">

	  Merry x-mas dear users! It's exactly one year since the release of the first
	  alpha version of SimpleMail and we made a big step in that time. We would like
	  to thank you for your support during the time and we are releasing the first
	  beta version of SimpleMail (V0.14)!

	  The changes are:
	  <list>
		<item>ARexx: added lots of commands.</item>
		<item>Signatures can now be stripped when replying.</item>
		<item>Folder names are now rendered in bold when containing new mail.</item>
		<item>Improved the wordwrap while quoting.</item>
		<item>Option to not quote empty lines.</item>
		<item>Your address is filtered out when replying a multiple recipient email.</item>
		<item>Modified the STARTTLS code following the suggestions from Jörg Strohmayer.</item>
		<item>Every folder can now have a default recipient address.</item>
		<item>Can now import address books from YAM.</item>
		<item>Implemented CC support in the Compose Message window.</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Fröhliche Weihnachten liebe User! Es ist nun genau ein Jahr her, seit der
	  Veröffentlichung von der ersten Version von SimpleMail und wir haben einen
	  grossen Schritt seitdem gemacht. Wir würden Euch gern für Euere Unterstüzung
	  in dieser Zeit danken und veröffentlichen nun die erste Beta-Version von
	  SimpleMail (V0.14)!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
	  <list>
		<item>ARexx: Viele neue Befehle hinzugefügt.</item>
		<item>Signaturen können vor dem Antworten entfernt werden.</item>
		<item>Folder-Namen werden fett gezeichnet wenn sie neue Mails enthalten.</item>
		<item>Wordwrap beim Quoten verbessert.</item>
		<item>Option nicht leere Zeilen zu zitieren.</item>
		<item>Die eigene Adresse wird beim Antworten an mehrere Empfänger entfernt.</item>
		<item>STARTTTLS wurde entsprechend den Hinweisen von  Jörg Strohmayer verändert.</item>
		<item>Jeder Folder kann einen voreingestellten Empfänger haben..</item>
		<item>Import von YAM-Adressbüchern ist nun möglich.</item>
		<item>Unterstützung für CC im Composefenster hinzugefügt.</item>
	  </list>

	</text>
  </entry>
  <entry date="2001/12/13">
	<text lang="en">
	  Added a link to a tutorial how to combine SimpleMail with
	  OpenURL or IBrowse by Stefan Martens. You find it in the links.
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Ein Link zu einem Tutorial von Stefan Martens wie man SimpleMail
	  mit OpenURL oder IBrowse kombinieren kann hinzugefügt. Er kann
	  in den Links gefunden werden.
	</text>

  </entry>
  <entry date="2001/12/07">
	<text lang="en">
	  Version 0.13 of SimpleMail released!

	  The changes are:
	  <list>
		<item>Included a real manual at last. Thanks to David Rey!</item>
		<item>SMTP over SSL.</item>
		<item>POP3 connections can be made secure with the STLS
		  command now. (RFC 2595)</item>
		<item>Primitive ARexx-port.</item>
		<item>Support for playing sounds.</item>
		<item>Taglines, the last %t in the signature will be replaced by a tagline.</item>
		<item>Folders holding unread mails are hilighted now.</item>
		<item>Localization.</item>
	  </list>
	  
	  Please note: if you downloaded your archive before 2001/12/08, 0:30am, there were 
	  informations
	  about the taglines missing in the guide so the guide has been replaced just
	  now. If you don't want to download the whole archive again, here is the changeg
	  paragraph:

	  Tick this box is you want SimpleMail to automatically add a random
	  tagline to every email you write. Simply insert a %t in the signature
	  and it will be replaced by a random tagline found in .taglines when
	  composing a mail.
	  
	  Sorry for the inconvience.
	  
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  SimpleMail Version 0.13 veröffentlicht!

	  Die Änderungen sind:
	  <list>
		<item>Endlich eine echte Anleitung! Danke an David Rey.</item>
		<item>SMTP over SSL.</item>
		<item>POP3-Verbindungen könnnen mit dem STLS-Kommando sicher gemacht werden. (RFC 2595)</item>
		<item>Primitiver ARexx-Port.</item>
		<item>Unterstützung für das Abspielen von Sounds.</item>
		<item>Taglines, das letzte %t in der signatur wird durch ein Tagline ersetzt.</item>
		<item>Folder mit ungelesenen Mails werden nun hevorgehoben.</item>
		<item>Lokalisation.</item>
	  </list>
	</text>

  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/11/10">
	<text lang="en">
	  Due to a exploit in MUI in combination with some PIPE-handlers
	  we have released a new version now, everybody actually should
	  update, as the old versions has a really nasty security-problem.

	  The changes are:
	  <list>
		<item>Fix for the MUI exploit.</item>
		<item> Messages can be also encrypted with PGP 2.6.x.</item>
		<item> Switching away of columns in the message list is possible now.
		  (save it via "Save Prefs") </item>
		<item> Completion of email-addresses improved. </item>
		<item> A small menu added to the readwindow that makes it possible to
		  see the raw mail. </item>
		<item> Mousewheelsupport of the readwindow is more tolerant now.</item>
		<item> The attachments are better identified if you have OS3.9
		  and DefIcons. You can double-click on an icon to start an
		  action (needs also OS3.9 and DefIcons, e.g. double-click on an
		  archive will start UnArc in the default config of DefIcons).</item>
		<item> Printing of messages and text-attachments is possible now.</item>
	  </list>
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Wegen einer Sicherheitslücke in MUI in Kombination mit einigen PIPE-Handlern
	  haben wir soeben eine neue Version, die u.a. diesen Fehler behebt, veröffentlicht.
	  Jeder sollte updaten, da die alte Version sehr üble Sicherheitsprobleme hat.

	  Die Änderungen sind:
	  <list>
		<item>Behebung der MUI-Sicherheitslücke.</item>
		<item>Mails können nun auch mit PGP 2.6.x verschlüsselt werden.</item>
		<item>Einzelne Spalten können in der Liste der Mails ausgeblendet werden.</item>
		<item>Vervollständigung der E-Mail-Adressen wurde verbessert.</item>
		<item>Ein kleines Menü wurde dem Lesefenster hinzugefügt und es ist
		möglich sich die Mails im Rohformat anzuschauen.</item>
		<item>Unterstützung von Mausrädern im Lesefenster ist nun toleranter.</item>
		<item>Die Anhänge werden jetzt besser erkannt, wenn man OS3.9 und
		DefIcons installiert hat. Durch Doppelklicks werden die eingestellten
		Standardaktionen gestartet (z.B. UnArc bei Archiven). </item>
		<item>Mails und Textanhänge können nun ausgedruckt werden.</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/10/21">
   <text lang="en">
	 Our user-mailinglist moves to http://freelist.org/ due to extensive spam.
   </text>

	<text lang="de">
	 Unsere Usermailingliste wurde wegen übermässigen Spam nach http://freelist.org/
	 verlegt.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/09/23">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.11 of SimpleMail has been released! Changes since last release were:
	  <list>
	   <item>UIDL Pop3 command support, so mails won't be downloaded twice</item>
	   <item>Improved Startup time</item>
	   <item>Bug fixes</item>
	  </list>
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Version 0.11 von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht! Änderungen seit der letzten Version:
	  <list>
	   <item>UIDL Pop3 Kommando wird unterstützt, so das Mails nicht zwei mal runtergeladen werden</item>
	   <item>Startzeit beschleunigt</item>
	   <item>Bug fixes</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/09/10">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.10 of SimpleMail has been released! Changes since last release were:
	  <list>
		<item>configurable headers for the read window</item>
		<item>can read message/rfc822 content type properly</item>
		<item>can decrypt encryptet pgp message using pgp 2.6.x</item>
		<item>minor other improvements</item>
		<item>filter has been improved</item>
		<item>wordwrapping for composed messages</item>
	  </list>
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Version 0.10 von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht! Änderungen seit der letzten Version:
	  <list>
		<item>Konfigurierbare Headers im Lesefenster</item>
		<item>Message/rfc822 Content Type Unterstützung</item>
		<item>Verschlüsselte Mail können gelesen werden (pgp 2.6.x)</item>
		<item>Kleinere andere Verbesserungen</item>
		<item>Verbesserter Filter</item>
		<item>Automatischer Zeilenumbruch im Schreibfenster</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/09/03">
   <text lang="en">
	  Version 0.9 of SimpleMail has been released! Changes since last release were:
	  <list>
	   <item>improved addressbook</item>
	   <item>predefined text phrases</item>
	   <item>periodical mail download</item>
	   <item>requires now the popplaceholder mui custom class</item>
	  </list>
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Version 0.9 von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht! Änderungen seit der letzten Version:
	  <list>
	   <item>Verbessertes Addressbuch</item>
	   <item>Vordefinierte Textphrasen</item>
	   <item>Periodischen Runterladen von Mails</item>
	   <item>Benötigt nun die  Popplaceholder Mui Custom Class</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/08/01">
	<text lang="en">
	  Version 0.8 of SimpleMail has been released! Changes since last release were:
	  <list>
	   <item>SSL support for POP3 Servers. Needs AmiSSL</item>
	   <item>POP3 servers can be individually deactivated and they are ignored</item>
	   <item>Menubar in the main window; needs to grow though</item>
	   <item>A new read setting, so that smilies can be replaced with images (images created by Richard Kapp)</item>
	   <item>Groups can be deleted now</item>
	  </list>
	  To report bugs please use now the <A HREF="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=115322&amp;group_id=15322&amp;func=browse">Bug Tracking System</A> and
	  if you want special new featutes the <A HREF="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=365322&amp;group_id=15322&amp;func=browse">Feature Request Tracking System</A> should be used.
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Version 0.8 von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht! Änderungen seit der letzten Version:
	  <list>
	   <item>SSL Unterstüzung für POP3 Server. AmiSSL wird dazu benötigt!</item>
	   <item>POP3 Server können individuell deaktiviert werden</item>
	   <item>Menüleiste im Hauptfenster.</item>
	   <item>Ein neue Lesefenstereinstellung, die es ermöglicht Smilies durch Bildchen ersetzen zu lassen (Bilder erstellt von Richard Kapp)</item>
	   <item>Gruppen können nun ebenfalls gelöscht werden</item>
	  </list>
	  Für Bug Reports sollte jetzt das <A HREF="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=115322&amp;group_id=15322&amp;func=browse">Bug Tracking System</A> und
	  Wünsche das <A HREF="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?atid=365322&amp;group_id=15322&amp;func=browse">Feature Request Tracking System</A> benutzt werden.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/06/29">
	<text lang="en">
	  Version 0.7 of SimpleMail has been released! Changes since last release were:
	  <list>
	   <item>the attachment icons weren't displayed on OSes with version below 3.5</item>
	   <item>signatures support</item>
	   <item>configurable greetings text when writing new mails</item>
	   <item>the fonts and colors for reading a mail can be configured</item>
	   <item>hierachical folders and folder images</item>
	  </list>
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Version 0.7 von SimpleMail wurde veröffentlicht! Änderungen seit der letzten Version:
	  <list>
	   <item>Die Icons der Anhänge wurden auf Betriebssytemversionen kleiner als 3.5 nicht dargestellt</item>
	   <item>Signaturen werden unterstützt</item>
	   <item>Konfigurierbare Begrüßungs- und Schlußtext beim Erstellen einer neuen E-Mail</item>
	   <item>Zeichensätze und Farben im Lesefenster einstellbar</item>
	   <item>Hierachische Ordner mit kleinen Bildchen</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/06/05">
	<text lang="en">
	  There was a problem with the last alpha of SimpleMail. It was compiled under WinUAE which seems not to be a good idea.
	  The results were crashed when starting an e-mail download. Please download the archive again. Sorry for this inconvenience.
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Es gab ein Problem bei der letzten Alpha von SimpleMail. Es wurde unter WinUAE kompiliert, was scheinbar keine so gute Idee war.
	  Es entstanden Abstürze beim Herunterladen von e-Mails. Das neue Archiv enthält eine hoffentlich fehlerfreiere Version.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/06/05">
	<text lang="en">
	  Again the homepage has been redesigned (mainly internal). 
	  There exists now also a german version of the homepage. Some passages are still in english. Additionally a new SimpleMail alpha has been released. Changes since last version:
	   <list>
		<item>Improved e-mail account configuration (multiple smtp servers)</item>
  <item>Can log into pop3 servers before sending e-mails</item>
  <item>Addressbook is now stored in xml</item>
  <item>Initial filter support</item>
  <item>New folders can be created within the gui and their settings are stored</item>
  <item>A lot of bug fixes</item>
	   </list>
	</text>

	<text lang="de">
	  Die Seiten wurden wieder etwas überarbeitet. Es gibt nun auch eine deutsche Version der Homepage, die jedoch noch nicht komplett fertig ist. Außerdem wurde eine neue Alpha Version von SimpleMail veröffentlicht. Änderungen seit der leztzen Version sind:
	   <list>
		<item>Verbesserte e-Mail Kontoverwaltung (u.a. auch mit mehereren SMTP Server)</item>
  <item>Kann sich in POP3 Server einwählen, bevor e-Mails versandt werden</item>
  <item>Addressbuch wird jetzt in XML gesichert</item>
  <item>Erste Filterunterstützung</item>
  <item>Ordner können jetzt auch innerhalb der GUI erstellt werden und die Einstellungen werden beibehalten.</item>
  <item>Viele Bugfixes</item>
	   </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/03/25">
	<text lang="en">
	  Introduced the new SimpleMail <a href="index.php?body=gallery">User Gallery</a>.
	  Alpha 0.5 has been released. New features are:
	  <list>
		<item>Configurable mail download selection added.</item>
		<item>Supports 8 bit mime mails (if a SMTP Server don't support them they are encoded on the fly).</item>
		<item>Improved the readwindow. Now used extensivly the SimpleHTML engine.</item>
		<item>Button images are cached now.</item>
		<item>Support of the new SimpleMail User Gallery.</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Die SimpleMail <a href="index.php?body=gallery">User Gallery</a> wurde eingerichtet. Alpha 0.5 wurde veröffentlicht. Neue Features sind:
	  <list>
		<item>Optionale Mailvorauswahl bevor die Mails runtergeladen werden</item>
		<item>Unterstützt das Senden von 8bit Mime Mails, falls der SMTP Server dies erlaubt</item>
		<item>Verbessertes Maillesefenster.</item>
		<item>Button Bilder werden jetzt nicht jedesmal neugeladen</item>
		<item>Unterstützung der SimpleMail User Gallery</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/02/25">
	<text lang="en">
	  A new alpha 0.4 has been released. Most important new feature is the possibility to
	  configure more then one POP3 server.
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Eine neue Alpha 0.4 Version wurde veröffentlicht. Wichtigstes neues Merkmal ist die Möglichkeit
	  zur Konfigurationen mehrerer POP3 Server.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/02/09">
	<text lang="en">
	  I (Hynek) am leaving today and will come back in April so send all mail you
	  send to me also to Sebastian as he will stay here.
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Hynek ist bis April nicht erreichbar, deshalb sollten alle Mails bzgl. SimpleMail die zu ihm gehen auch an Sebastian
	  geschickt werden.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/02/06">
	<text lang="en">
	  New frequently asked questions added to the <a href="index.html?part=faq">FAQ</a>.
	</text>
	<text lang="de">
	  Neue häufig gestellte Fragen der <a href="index.php?part=faq">FAQ</a> hinzugefügt.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/02/05">
	<text lang="en">
	  Alpha-Version 0.3 released! This time we have added quiet a bunch of new
	  features:
	  <list>
		<item>Forward button.</item>
		<item>The main window has two different views which are switchable
		  within the mainwindow.</item>
		<item>Improved the composewindow (some buttons added, also a undo/redo).</item>
		<item>The "To" button in the addressbook works now.</item>
		<item>Group mails (mails with multiple recipients), mails with attachments,
		  important mails can now easily identified.</item>
		<item>Added a small context menu for the mailtreelist, mails can now be
		  marked and hold.</item>
		<item>Added the possibility to use your IP-addresss as you domain in
		  the HELO/EHLO dialog. (no X-Authentification-Warning headers anymore).</item>
		<item>Added smtp-auth according to rfc2554.</item>
		<item>It is now possible to specify which port you would like to use on
		  the servers instead of 25 (SMTP) and 110 (POP3).</item>
		<item>Other smaller improvements and bug fixes.</item>
	  </list>
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/01/26">
	<text>
	  New frequently asked question added to the <a href="index.html?faq">FAQ</a>.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/01/26">
	<text>
	  Added some banners for your homepages made by Richard Wagenführer.
	  You can find them in the <a href="index.html?downloads">downloads-section</a>.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/01/23">
	<text>
	  The homepage moves to http://simplemail.sourceforge.net/. A completly new
	  design is introduced.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2001/01/14">
	<text>
	  The second alpha version 0.2 is released.
	</text>
  </entry>

  <entry date="2000/12/24">
	<text>
	  The first alpha version 0.1 is released.
	</text>
  </entry>

</news>



